[
  {
    "front": "안녕하세요.",
    "back": "Hello!"
  },
  {
    "front": "감사합니다.",
    "back": "Thank you."
  },
  {
    "front": "안녕히 계세요.",
    "back": "Goodbye."
  },
  {
    "front": "안녕히 가세요.",
    "back": "Goodbye."
  },
  {
    "front": "죄송합니다.",
    "back": "I apologize."
  },
  {
    "front": "저기요.",
    "back": "Excuse me!"
  },
  {
    "front": "물이에요.",
    "back": "It's water."
  },
  {
    "front": "가방이에요.",
    "back": "It's a bag."
  },
  {
    "front": "저예요.",
    "back": "It's me."
  },
  {
    "front": "이거 책이에요.",
    "back": "This is a book."
  },
  {
    "front": "이거 카메라예요.",
    "back": "This is a camera."
  },
  {
    "front": "이거 뭐예요?",
    "back": "What is this?"
  },
  {
    "front": "이거 물이에요.",
    "back": "This is water."
  },
  {
    "front": "네, 맞아요.",
    "back": "Yes, that's right."
  },
  {
    "front": "우유 아니에요.",
    "back": "It's not milk."
  },
  {
    "front": "저 학생 아니에요.",
    "back": "I'm not a student."
  },
  {
    "front": "그거 고양이 아니에요.",
    "back": "It's not a cat."
  },
  {
    "front": "목소리&nbsp;좋아요.",
    "back": "Your voice is good."
  },
  {
    "front": "물 있어요.",
    "back": "I have water."
  },
  {
    "front": "시간 있어요?",
    "back": "Do you have time?"
  }
]